

NAGARAJ.C.H (NAGALINGA.C.H)

YOGA KISHORA; YOGA KUMARA; YOGA RAKSHAKA

With lifelong yoga practice and over 8 years of teaching experience, I believe in the healing power of yogasana (yoga poses) as a holistic approach to good health and longevity. If you invest in your practice, Yoga is your doctor. Amen to that!

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 26th August 1990 Language: English, Indian Language

Gender: Male Mail: omnagarajyoga@gmail.com

Passport No.: R9103536 Phone: 158 0066 1043

+91 9980004317 Indian Nationality:

WORK EXPERIENCE

S .G.S International Yoga Foundation, Colleage & Research Centre(R), Bangalore Yoga Teacher.	2006-2007
Jagadguru Sri Shivanand Vidyapeeth(R), Kundgol. Yoga Teacher	2007-2014
Just Yoga Studio, Shanghai	2015-2017
Yoga Teacher Vivekanandayoga China(Shanghai)	2015-2017
Yoga Teacher Yogavashishth in Delhi	2018-2019
Yoga Teacher	2020-
EDUCATION	

Mahatma Gandhi Central University,Bihar	
Bachelor of Arts	2012-2015
SGS INTERNATIONAL YOGA FOUNDATION COLLEGE AND RESEARCH CENTER (R.)	
Diploma in yoga	2013-2014

CERTIFICATE

Sta te Level Yogasana Championship Certificate

International Level Open Yogasana Championship Certificate

S t ate NLeavteiol nOapl eYno gYaosgaan Ca hOapmepni oGnesnheipra Cl

eCrhtaifmicaptioe nship Certificate

In ternSattaioten aLel veLle Yvoegl asOapnean C hYaomgpaisoannsah ipC Chearmtipfiicoantesh ip

State Level Open Yoga Championship Certificate

Certificate of Participation in International Yoga Coordination Ce

HONORS

Awards:

Won 1st place in National & International level Yoga competition

Won 1st place in District, Thaluk & State level Yoga competition

Won 2nd place in International Level Open Yogasana Competition 2008

Won 2nd place in National Yogashana Open General Championship 2006

Won 2nd place in State Level Yogasana Championship 2006

Won 2nd place in State Level Open Yoga Championship 2010

Won 4th place in world level Yoga competition

TEACHING STYLE OF YOGA

ADVANCED YOGA PERFORMANCE IN

Hatha Yoga

Vinyasa

Advanced Asana

Slimming Yoga

Props Yoga

Power Yoga

Therapic Yoga

Arele yog

Back Bending

Forward Bending

Balancing

Twisting